I want to appeal to you that I too need healing.
Hallelujah!
The moment I stretch my hand to pray for the sick, the one that is sick in me...
The SCOAN Sunday Service
The one that has cold will just...
So, you have to allow me to go and pray so that that one can leave me.
The name of that one is T.B. Joshua.
But the one that you are coming to meet is the Prophet.
By His stripes, we are healed.
I love praying when the environment is calm.
Because of that, I prefer praying when it is night, in a quiet place.
This time, the cold was so much and I had to go extreme,
exposing myself to that cold when I was praying.
That is how I got my cold.
Hallelujah!
It is your turn now to tell me how you normally get your cold.
Who is ready to tell me here?
If rain beats me, I get cold.
Oh my God. Thank you.
You know today that T.B. Joshua and Prophet are entirely two different natures.
They are entirely two different persons.
Each time there is a miracle, you will always see me, "Please, let's move!"
I will not start asking, "Hee, how does it happen?" - No!
The work of miracle is not from T.B. Joshua; it is from God.
It is not the work of T.B. Joshua.
Thank you.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
I have a stiff neck due to cervical spondylosis.
I am using a neck collar. I have been having this problem for the past 12 years.
Help me, Man of God.
It has stopped me from going to work.
I can't do the work I used to do when I was still healthy.
Man of God, please, help me.
When you receive your healing, you say, "We are healed"; not, "I am healed".
I am healed!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
When you receive your healing now, when you want to testify, you say,
"We are healed; including T.B. Joshua!"
You people normally say, "I am healed, I am healed", as if we too are not healed.
We are healed, including T.B. Joshua.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
This man, you are not serious.
Ok, thank You.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Remove it.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Turn your neck.
Healed In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus. I am healed.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
You said, "I am healed". Are you removing me from the healing?
This man is very stubborn.
I said, "We are healed". He said, "I am healed".
When you say, "We are healed", it means I will get my healing too.
Continue shaking until you know the right thing to say.
We have disturbed him for long.
What have you done to him?
Since 1997, we have been sent to kill him.
This is a different man oo.
Why? The man is a very strong man - we would have killed him.
We want to kill him because of his education.
Who are you in this body?
I am lucifer.
He is healed. Can you carry lucifer here.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Set Free In Jesus' Name
Stand up.
What do you want to say now?
Thank You, Jesus.
Brethren, help me to thank God for having healed me after a long time of trouble.
That is for forgetting what I told you.
Thank You, Jesus, for having delivered me.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
This man is very selfish. Carry your miracle.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Man of God, I am called Grace, from Uganda. I have difficulty in walking.
I use a lumbar corset. I have hypertension and leg numbness.
You are healed, isn't it?
Amen.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
I am healed. We are healed.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Stand up.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
It's alright. You can go.
Healed In Jesus' Name
I am healed. Thank You, Jesus.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Come on!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Look here!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Stand up.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
You can go.
Thank You, Jesus. We are healed, including T.B. Joshua.
Healed In Jesus' Name
Thank you, mama.
Man of God, help me.
I have hernia on my stomach.
It has been five years.
I have been operated three times.
Please, papa, help me.
Ok, it's alright.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Ok, stand up. Come on.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
You can stand up.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus. We are healed.
Thank You! For many years!
Thank You, Jesus! Thank You, Lord!
Thank You, we are healed.
Man of God, help me. I have osteoarthritis all over the body.
I have difficulty in walking. I have osteoporosis for 12 years now.
It incapacitates me. I am a teacher, and I have difficulty to stand in the class.
Thank you, teacher. Thank you for taking care of our children.
Thank you.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Thank You, I am healed.
We are healed, including T.B. Joshua.
Man of God, please, help me. I have a shoulder dislocation for 9 years.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Remove it.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Come on.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus. We are healed.
Man of God, please, help me. I have arthritis of the back and the knees.
I cannot walk.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Healed In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Lord. Thank You, I am healed.
Thank You, we are healed.
Man of God, help me. I have difficulty in walking, and a severe pain in my back - up to my left side.
I even have...
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Healed In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus. We are healed.
Man of God, help me. I have difficulty in walking.
I have disc prolapse with canal stenosis.
I am using crutches to walk.
I use a lumbar corset to support my back.
Man of God, I am in serious pain.
Please, help me. I use this to warm by back so that I can have some sleep.
If I don't do that, I can't sleep at all.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Come. Come to me.
You can go.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Leave her. Let her stand up.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You can go, walk majestically.
Healed In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus. We are healed.
Thank You, Jesus. I can walk now.
Thank You, Jesus. I no longer need crutches.
Healed In Jesus' Name
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Esther Tetteh from Ghana. I can't walk.
Ok, it's alright. Thank you.
She can't do anything. She can't bend her knees.
She can't even take care of her grandchildren.
Look here!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Can you remove it.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Look here.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Stand up and walk.
Thank You, Jesus.
Thank You, Jesus. We are healed.
I can use my hand now. Thank You, Jesus.
Thank You, Jesus.
Please, help me. I am from Uganda.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Man of God, please help me.
It's alright.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Can you remove it.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Come on. Look here.
Stand up.
Go this way.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Healed In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus.
Thank You, Jesus, for healing me.
Hallelujah.
Healed In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus. Oh! Ha! Hallelujah!
You show me the Bible today.
I am Gifty. I come from Ghana.
I have difficulty in walking. I have osteoarthritis. I am using a knee brace.
It's alright.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Stand up.
Healed In Jesus' Name
You see - you that are not being prayed for, are the ones that are more healed.
Listen!
You receive more blessing than the people who are being prayed for.
Let me tell you the reason.
You pay attention to what is happening.
That attention is increasing your faith.
Thank You, Jesus. We are healed.
You pay attention to what is going on and that automatically draws you closer to God,
than even the people that are being prayed for.
I'm telling you.
Each miracle enhances your faith.
You find yourself growing bigger in God.
You are closer to God than the people that are receiving healing.
Each miracle reminds you of who you were, who you are and who you will be.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Are you with me?
Tell your neighbour, "Each miracle reminds me of who I was, who I am and who I will be".
The SCOAN Sunday Service
"Oh, I thought it was like this; right I can see."
"I never knew God is the same. What I read in the Bible, I can see it clearly."
"Oh my God, I am sorry".
It's now very clear to you, "Oh yes, I can see why these things are being persecuted".
The SCOAN Sunday Service
What people do not know, they persecute.
What they know, they destroy.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Whatever they don't know about you, and you are doing it and it is happening,
and they are trying to know how you do it and they don't know how you do it,
they will persecute you.
But if they know how you do it, they will kill you and take it up.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
So therefore, those things God has given you as a mystery -
mystery means like you market women, business man,
you have whatever career - are you a doctor, lawyer - and you are flourishing,
and some of your colleagues keep asking themselves, "How manage?"
This is going like this way for you and it is not going that way for them.
They are trying to know how you are doing it and they don't know.
They will persecute you and call you names and do all sort of things.
But if they know exactly how you are doing it, they will kill and destroy you.
That is what you too are going through.
What you are seeing now, it is only God - just only God!
Why?
Because it does not cost anything; it's effortless.
And what is effortless, you cannot demand money for it.
But because you want to collect money, you now try to sweat,
you try to show some labour and effort; to show you have laboured and suffered,
so that you can demand for money.
Those things that are effortless - if you are able to exercise such a thing in the presence of people,
you can't ask them to bring money.
Money is all about labour.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
That is it. I am giving my testimony.
I come from Namibia.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Ok, it's alright.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Come on.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Come on. Look here.
Healed In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus.
Wonderful!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Healed In Jesus' Name
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus. We are healed.
Man of God, please help my son. He has a mental disorder.
I am from Minnesota, the United States.
Man of God, please help my son.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Healed In Jesus' Name
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Come on. Sit down.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Healed In Jesus' Name
I cannot do anything due to lumbar spondylosis.
I am a nurse. I have diabetes and I am using a lumbar corset.
Please, Man of God, help me.
Man of God, please, help my mother. For the past seven years, she has been like this.
She has lumbar spondylosis. She cannot walk or do anything for the past seven years.
She is using a lumbar corset to support her. Help my mother.
These are the drugs she has been taking.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering
Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Healed In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Jesus.
Thank You, Jesus. I can walk.
Thank You, Jesus. My mother is walking now. As you can see, she is walking.
The SCOAN Sunday Service